Logan Darriel Collins

Full Stack Blockchain & Web Developer

Hermes8527@gmail.com

L1 (516) 654-4426 https://github.com/hermes8527 Q Lyons, GA, US

Summary

I am a self-motivated, self-learning and passionate developer with high skills, rich experience and passion in Blockchain & Web development. I have 8+ years of experience in Web Development using several Frameworks and languages like React.js, Node.js, LitElement, Laravel, Golang and PHP.

In 2018, I was really excited with Blockchain technology and tried to learn principles and development theories. I am proficient in developing Smart Contracts in Solidity and integrating Web3 using Web3.js and Ethers.js. Now I'm learning another chains like Solana, Polkadot and Rust language.

I always love to work with team and I'm eager to learn new technologies and make great things to make people surprised.

SKILLS

Blockchain: Blockchain Principles and Architecture, Ethereum, Solidity, Smart Contract, Web3, Ethers.js,

Hardhat, Truffle

Front-End: ReactJS, JavaScript(ES2015-2019), TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, Responsive

Web Design, LitElement

Back-End: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Laravel, Golang

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB

API Integration: RESTful API, GraphQL

Testing: Unit Testing, E2E Testing, Mocha, Jest, Cypress, Karma, Jasmine

Version Control Systems: Git, SVN DevOps: Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD

Other: Agile Software Development, Precise Communication, Team Work, Pressure Resistance

Experience



Full Stack Blockchain Developer

TotemFi(Sparkworld)

Mar 2022 - Jan 2024

- Clarified main features of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator projects and Designed NFT Marketplace and Aggregator collaborating with CTO
- Developed the Smart Contracts of NFT Marketplace in Golang and unit test scripts based in Hardhat framework
- Passed the Smart Contract Audit and fixed security and performance issues
- Found and Implemented Methods to fetch sale data and buy NFTs from several NFT Marketplaces



Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

May 2019 - Mar 2022

- Joined to the company as Full Stack Blockchain Developer
- Researched practical principles to enable Smart Contracts on Firo Chain
- Designed the Firo Bridge to synchronize transaction data between Firo Chain and FiroVM Chain to enable
 Smart Contracts like Ethereum
- Developed the Bridge in Golang and stored all the transaction data in PostgreSQL database



Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

Apr 2016 - Mar 2019

- Started to work as internship to learn the company culture and development methodologies for half an year
- Worked as a Frontend developer focused on Laravel and React.js implmenting frontend with the design for a year
- Got the Backend developer role to develop Backend in Node.js and Laravel and design the database and APIs

Education



DePaul University

Master of Science (B.S.) - Computer Science Apr 2012 - Jul 2016

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS



Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate 2019



IBM Full Stack Software Developer Professional Certificate

2022